Sierra Club, Atlantic Chapter; Records apap130
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Publications, Non-Sierra Club, 1979-1997; 7; 2.9 cubic ft.
  - Reports, 1980-1996; 7.2; 1.6 cubic ft.
    - National Center for Policy Alternatives Legislative Sourcebook on the Environment, 1986 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 28)
    - New York City Department of Sanitation A Comprehensive Solid Waste Management Plan for New York City and Draft Generic Environmental Impact Statement, 1992 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 29)
    - New York State Assembly Report on the Validity of 16 NYCRR Part 815, 1991 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 30)
    - New York State Assembly Energy Committee New York's Persistent Energy Crisis: The Consequences of Overuse and the Availability of Power Through Energy Efficiency, 1991 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 31)
    - New York State Attorney General New York Under a Cloud: The Need to Prevent Toxic Chemical Accidents, 1989 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 32)
    - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, Amendments to 6 NYCRR Part 218 Emission Standards for Motor Vehicles and Motor Vehicle Engines: Assessment of Public Comments, 1992 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 33)
    - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, Draft Adjudication Plan, Office of Hearings, Submitted Pursuant to Governor's Executive Order No.131, 1990 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 34)
    - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, Draft New York State Solid Waste Management Plan 1990-1991 Update (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 35)
    - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, Environmental Regulatory Program Title 6, New York Codes, Rules and Regulations, Undated (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 36)
    - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, Environmental Regulatory Program Title 6, New York Codes, Rules and Regulations, Undated (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 37)
    - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, Great Lakes Agenda Issues and Recommendations, 1987 April (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 38)
    - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, Greenline and Urbanline Parks Conference, 1983 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 39)
    - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, New York State Air Quality Report: Ambient Air Monitoring System, 1990 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 40)
    - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, New York State Solid Waste Management Plan 1987-1988 Update (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 41)
    - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, 1990 Clean Air Act Information, ca. 1990 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 42)
    - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, Reasonably Available Control Technology for Oxides of Nitrogen, 1994 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 43)
    - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, Revised 6 NYCRR Part 360 Solid Waste Management Facilities (Draft), 1988 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 44)
    - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, Revised 6 NYCRR Part 219 Incinerators (Draft), 1988 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 45)
    - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, 6 NYCRR Part 360 Regulations: Solid Waste Management Facilities and 6 NYCRR Part 219 Regulations: Air Emissions from Incinerator Facilities, 1988 (Box 2 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 46)
    - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, 6 NYCRR Part 360 Solid Waste Management Facilities, 1998 (Box 3 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 1)
    - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, Toxic Chemical Accidents in New York State: 1990 Data Summary, 1991 (Box 3 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 2)
    - New York State Department of Transportation The Next Generation: Transportation Choices for the 21st Century, 1996 (Box 3 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 3)
    - New York State Emergency Response Commission 1991 Toxic Release Inventory (TRI) Review, 1992 (Box 3 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 4)
    - New York State Energy Office Analysis of Carbon Reduction in New York State, 1991 (Box 3 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 5)
    - New York State Energy Office Draft New York State Energy Plan 1991 Biennial Update Volume I: Summary Report (Box 3 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 6)
    - New York State Energy Office Draft New York State Energy Plan 1991 Biennial Update Volume II: Assessment Reports (Box 3 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 7)
    - New York State Energy Office Draft New York State Energy Plan 1991 Biennial Update Volume III: Issue Reports (Box 3 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 8)
    - New York State Energy Office Draft New York State Energy Plan 1991 Biennial Update Volume IV: Draft Environmental Impact Statement (Box 3 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 9)
    - New York State Energy Office New York State Energy Plan Volumes I-III, 1992 (Box 3 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 10)
    - New York State Energy Office Draft New York State Energy Plan Executive Summary, 1994 (Box 3 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 11)
    - New York State Energy Office Draft New York State Energy Plan Volume I: Summary Report, 1994 (Box 3 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 12)
    - New York State Energy Office Draft New York State Energy Plan Volume II: Issue Reports, 1994 (Box 3 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 13)
    - New York State Energy Office Draft New York State Energy Plan Volume III: Supply Assessments, 1994 (Box 3 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 14)
    - New York State Energy Research and Development Authority, Gas DSM and Fuel-Switching: Opportunities and Experiences, 1994 (Box 3 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 15)
    - New York State Legislature Environmental Education Volume I, 1989 (Box 3 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 16)
    - New York State Legislature Financing Superfund: Dollars and Sense, 1991 (Box 3 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 17)
    - New York State Senate New York State's Adoption of the California Automobile Emissions Program, 1991 (Box 3 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 18)
    - State and Territorial Air Pollution Program Administrators/Association of Local Air Pollution Control Officials, Summary of the Clean Air Amendments of 1990 (Box 3 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 19)
    - Trust for Public Land Protecting the Source: Land Conservation and the Future of America's Drinking Water, ca. 1996 (Box 3 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 20)
    - United States Environmental Protection Agency Building Air Quality: A Guide for Building Owners and Facility Managers, 1991 (Box 3 (7-Publications, Non-Sierra Club), Folder 21)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1983-1990; 8; 9 videos, 1 film reel, 1 audiotape
  This series includes videotapes and film reels produced by or on topics of interest to the Atlantic Chapter dating from the 1980s. Among them are several public service announcements produced by the Sierra Club, television news reports, and a Canadian film on acid rain.
  Arranged by format.
  - "Voices From the Garden", Undated (Vhs 1)
  - Hometown Advantage, Undated (Vhs 2)
  - The Arctic National Wildlife Refuge: America's Last Great Refuge, Undated (Vhs 3)
  - "Global Warming", 1990 (Vhs 4)
  - "To Lend a Helping Hand", Undated (Vhs 5)
  - "Nuclear Power Industry Transportation Claims Debunked", 1992 (Vhs 6)
  - Sierra Club Public Service Announcements, 1983 (Umatic 1)
    Changing World #1.
    Timeless America #1.
    Changing World #2.
    Timeless America #2.
    Yosemite.
    Changing World #3.
    Timeless America #3.
  - Sierra Club Public Service Announcements, 1983 (Umatic 2)
    "Barrier Beach".
    "Whole Earth".
    "Strip Mining".
  - Acid Rain, CBS, Undated (Umatic 3)
  - Acid Rain: Requiem or Recovery, National Film Board of Canada, Film, 996", 26:50 (with Response Sheets), 1987; Undated (Film 1)
  - Sierra Club Energy Conservation Public Service Announcements, Jim Belsey, Sierra Club - Mills Tower, S.F. [San Francisco], CA 94104, Produced by Environmental Interchange, San Geronimo, CA, Music by Beaver & Krause, "Nonesuch Guide to Electronic Music, Audiotape, Undated (Reel 1)
    "Overview", :60.
    "Environmental Emphasis", :30.
    "Eliminate Waste", :20.
    "Consider the Alternative", :10.
    "Environmental Emphasis", without music, :30.
    "Eliminate Waste", without music, :20.